{
    "quiz": {
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 161,
                "_id": "07-01",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "A basic step in the budgeting process is to estimate project cost based on the scope of the work, historical records, and:",
                "refPage": "174",
                "possible0": "current costs.",
                "possible1": "funds available.",
                "possible2": "program proposals.",
                "possible3": "projected future costs.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 162,
                "_id": "07-02",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "While the FLSE II will not be directly responsible for governmental accounting when working with the budget, the FLSE II will likely cooperate with:",
                "refPage": "174",
                "possible0": "contractors.",
                "possible1": "a tax expert.",
                "possible2": "the board of directors.",
                "possible3": "the agency or jurisdiction finance officer.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 163,
                "_id": "07-03",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What allow financial officers, agency executives, and jurisdiction executives to compare items with similar features and functions in measuring costs and benefits of individual programs?",
                "refPage": "174",
                "possible0": "COLA and evaluations",
                "possible1": "Resources and historical records",
                "possible2": "Scope of work and formated information",
                "possible3": "GAAP and a standardized chart of accounts",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 164,
                "_id": "07-04",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What a program hopes to accomplish during the budget period and how to go about meeting those goals may be documented by the FLSE II in the:",
                "refPage": "175",
                "possible0": "scope of work.",
                "possible1": "agency summary.",
                "possible2": "chart of accounts.",
                "possible3": "jurisdiction budget request.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 165,
                "_id": "07-05",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What type of data may often provide a good starting point for the FLSE II to determine future costs of resources?",
                "refPage": "176",
                "possible0": "Special",
                "possible1": "Outside",
                "possible2": "Required",
                "possible3": "Historical",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 166,
                "_id": "07-06",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "Creating a _____ for a specific program or activity is very similar to developing an evaluation plan for addressing a risk issue.",
                "refPage": "176",
                "possible0": "scope of work",
                "possible1": "budget proposal",
                "possible2": "marketing survey",
                "possible3": "memorandum of understanding",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 167,
                "_id": "07-07",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "Why is it important for the FLSE II to be concise, grammatical, and accurate when giving a budget presentation?",
                "refPage": "177",
                "possible0": "Fiscal year restrictions",
                "possible1": "Personnel evaluation requirements",
                "possible2": "Organization mission statement content",
                "possible3": "Time allotted for a budget presentation may be defined",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 168,
                "_id": "07-08",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What is a period of time that a government uses for budget and accounting purposes?",
                "refPage": "177",
                "possible0": "Tax season",
                "possible1": "A fiscal year (FY)",
                "possible2": "Review and renew",
                "possible3": "A calendar year (CY)",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 169,
                "_id": "07-09",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "An essential component of fire and life safety education is to have _____ to address risk.",
                "refPage": "179",
                "possible0": "legal council",
                "possible1": "internal partners",
                "possible2": "adequate resources",
                "possible3": "in-kind contributions",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 170,
                "_id": "07-10",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What are gifts of money to a nonprofit, tax-exempt private organization, government organization, or individuals and companies?",
                "refPage": "180",
                "possible0": "Grants",
                "possible1": "Scholarships",
                "possible2": "No interest loans",
                "possible3": "In-kind contributions",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 171,
                "_id": "07-11",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "As opposed to monetary grants, _____ are gifts of services, time, staff, or products.",
                "refPage": "180",
                "possible0": "tax exemptions",
                "possible1": "competitive grants",
                "possible2": "in-kind contributions",
                "possible3": "memorandums of understanding",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 172,
                "_id": "07-12",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "Regulations or protocols used to govern how an organization spends money are used as a(an) _____ put in place as a safeguard for public funds.",
                "refPage": "181",
                "possible0": "bond",
                "possible1": "equity confirmation",
                "possible2": "request for proposal",
                "possible3": "checks and balances system",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 173,
                "_id": "07-13",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What is developed to define an organization's needs and allows manufacturers or authorized vendors to determine if they can meet bid specifications?",
                "refPage": "181",
                "possible0": "Evaluation protocol",
                "possible1": "Pre-budget analysis",
                "possible2": "Purchase order (PO)",
                "possible3": "Request for proposal (RFP)",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 174,
                "_id": "07-14",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What do some organizations use to allow vendors to invoice for monies owed?",
                "refPage": "182",
                "possible0": "Public policy",
                "possible1": "Financial aid",
                "possible2": "Purchase order (PO)",
                "possible3": "Request for proposal (RFP)",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 175,
                "_id": "07-15",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "A well-developed _____ contains a system of laws, regulatory measures, and courses of action.",
                "refPage": "182",
                "possible0": "public policy",
                "possible1": "business plan",
                "possible2": "risk evaluation",
                "possible3": "purchase order",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 176,
                "_id": "07-16",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What type of personnel evaluation is an ongoing process throughout an employee's career?",
                "refPage": "184",
                "possible0": "Narrative",
                "possible1": "Formative",
                "possible2": "Cumulative",
                "possible3": "Summative",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 177,
                "_id": "07-17",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "What are formal systematic procedures for appraising employees' abilities and accomplishments within the organization?",
                "refPage": "185",
                "possible0": "Skill review",
                "possible1": "Motivational programs",
                "possible2": "Personnel evaluation programs",
                "possible3": "Permanent record documentation",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 178,
                "_id": "07-18",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "FLSEs should ensure subordinates understand the relevant _____ upon which they will be evaluated.",
                "refPage": "185",
                "possible0": "goals",
                "possible1": "feedback",
                "possible2": "monitoring",
                "possible3": "performance standards",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 179,
                "_id": "07-19",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "The job-performance evaluation is an opportunity to reinforce positive performance or to generate change in an employee's behavior in order to:",
                "refPage": "185",
                "possible0": "control the evaluation process.",
                "possible1": "meet the organization's expectations.",
                "possible2": "change the content of the evaluation.",
                "possible3": "focus on the accomplishments of the employee.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 180,
                "_id": "07-20",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "FLSE IIs must be familiar with all _____ relevant to personnel evaluations.",
                "refPage": "188",
                "possible0": "trends",
                "possible1": "proposals",
                "possible2": "legislative provisions",
                "possible3": "statutory requirements",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 181,
                "_id": "07-21",
                "chapterId": 7,
                "question": "Personnel evaluations must include definite identifiable criteria based on:",
                "refPage": "188",
                "possible0": "results of previous evaluations.",
                "possible1": "a positive working atmosphere.",
                "possible2": "probationary period requirements.",
                "possible3": "the quality or quantity of work or on specific performances.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            }
        ]
    }
}
